School Address: 1210 W Dayton St, WI

# Fu Chun Hsieh (Frederic) fhsieh5@wisc.edu (202)818-9704

Home Address: 1510 Tripp Circle, WI

I'm a junior student in CS and have 5+ years of experience in programming. I am passionate about my academic studies and my workout routine. Having effective communication and finishing tasks efficiently are the greatest strengths I have. I'm also creative in ways of solving (programming) problems and brainstorming ideas.

#### **Education**

## **University of Wisconsin - Madison**

Madison, WI

B.S. in Computer Science

2023 - present

 Relevant coursework: Neural Networks, Comp Sci 300, linear algebra, Science Communication

### American University

Washington, D.C.

Liberal Studies, Computer Science GPA: 3.93/4.0

2021 - 2023

- Dean's list
- Relevant coursework: Machine learning with cybersecurity, Data Structures and Algorithms, Computer Programming I, II, III, Calculus I, II.
- English studies: College Writing I, II

## Experience

## **Audio Reverse-Engineering Using Machine Learning**

Washington, D.C.

2023

Researcher, Author (language: Python)

- Using machine learning models like random forest, CNN, and XGBoost to classify converted audio to original audio and rebuild the audio
- Optimized the accuracy from .3 to .82 using the CNN model and wrote a report about the research project

#### **Personal Website**

Madison, Wisconsin

Author (language: html, CSS, JavaScript)

Ongoing

- A website that contains information about my project and portfolio
- Online library that allows people to find and borrow books from people nearby

## **American University Student Council**

Washington, D.C.

**Student Councilor** 

2022-2023

- Represent international and L&S students to meet with the dean and provide critical feedback on college plans biweekly
- Be the communication liaison between school and the student body

#### Leadership

## **Taiwanese Student Association**

Washington, D.C.

2021-2023

- Plan and execute cultural festivals, workshops, and social gatherings, catering to Taiwanese students and those who are interested in Taiwanese culture.
- Led a team of 5 committee members, fostering collaboration and delegating tasks to ensure the successful implementation of events.

#### **Consult Your Community**

Washington, D.C.

2022-2023

Member, Consultant

**Events Coordinator** 

• Meet with clients and help local businesses sketch out future plans

 Conduct research about opportunities to grow businesses and design possible commercial campaigns or events

#### Other Skills

Mandarin - fluent speaker and writer

C++ - 4 years experiences, fluent in object-oriented programming, done 400+ problems

**Python -** 3 years experiences, specialized in data processing and machine learning applications

**Fitness and Nutrition Plans -** 3 years experiences, work out regularly and manage to learn some knowledge about nutriology